Delaney, James Joseph; Papers apap241
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislative Files, 1950-1978, 1; 9.65 cubic ft.
  - Chemical Additives in Food and Drug, 1950-1978; 1.1
    - S-79, sorrespondence, 1959 March (Box 5 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 13)
    - Saccharin, 1970 February-1970 June (Box 5 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 14)
    - Saccharin, 1977 June-1978 January (Box 5 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 15-17)
    - Saccharin press conference by Food and Drug Administration, 1977 April (Box 5 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 18)
    - Saccharin final report, July 1978, 1978 July (Box 5 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 19-20)
    - Saffiotti, Dr. Umberto, 1970 April (Box 5 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 21)
    - Select Committee, 1950-1952 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 22)
    - Select Committee, November-December 1954, 1954 November-1954 December (Box 5 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 23-24)
    - Select Committee, cities and civic bodies, 1953-1954 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 25)
    - Select Committee clippings and research materials, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 26)
    - Select Committee, correspondence, 1950-1960 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 27)
    - Select Committee, endorsements, 1951 April-1952 May (Box 5 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 28)
    - Select Committee, hearings, 1951 October-1952 November (Box 5 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 29)
    - Select Committee, legislation, 81st-82nd, 1951-1952 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 1)
    - Select Committee, libraries, 1953 January-1954 August (Box 6 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 2)
    - Select Committee, releases. Includes photograph, 1951 April-1952 June (Box 6 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 3)
    - Select Committee, speech notes, 1951 January (Box 6 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 4)
    - Select Committee, universities and doctors, 1952-1960 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 5)
    - The Silent Spring of Rachel Carson, CBS reports. Includes transcript, 1963 April (Box 6 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 6)
    - Spinrad, Mrs. Rhea, 1966 March-1972 August (Box 6 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 7)
    - Stahile, Toni, cosmetics, 1966 June-1972 February (Box 6 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 8)
    - Stewart, Dr. Howard L., 1970 August (Box 6 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 9)
    - Vitamin supplement, 1966-1969 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 10-11)
    - Wiley, Dr. Harvey, 1962 July (Box 6 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 12)
    - Zaratzian, Dr. Virginia, Food and Drug Administration, 1971-1972 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 13)
  - Education Files, 1952-1978; 1.2
    - The American School Board Journal, 1971 June-1971 July (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 1)
    - Archdiocese of New York, integration in Catholic schools, 1966 August (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 2)
    - The Blaine Amendment, 1970 January (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 3)
    - Catholics in politics and public office, 1954 January (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 4)
    - Catholic organization publications. Includes American National Catholic Weekly Review; The Catholic Historical Review; Catholic Standard and Times; National Catholic Welfare Conference, Catholic School Administrators Association of New York State, National Conference of Christian and Jews, 1950-1975 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 5-6)
    - Blum, Reverend Virgil C., 1962 January-1967 April (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 7-8)
    - Carey, Hugh, L., 1962 April-1963 September (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 9)
    - Citizens for Educational Freedom, 1970 February-1972 August (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 10)
    - Citizens relief for education by income tax, memorandum, 1972 September (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 10A)
    - Clippings, 1894 June (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 11)
    - Clippings, educational video, 1967 January (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 12)
    - Clippings, for and against federal aid to education, 1955-1970 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 13)
    - Clippings, federal aid to education, 1960-1965 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 14-15)
    - Clippings, federal aid to education, 1970-1972 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 16)
    - Clippings, Office of Economic Opportunity/ Junior G.I. bill, 1969-1970 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 17)
    - Clippings, Our Sunday Visitor, 1960-1965 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 18)
    - Clippings, Kent State, 1970-1971 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 19)
    - Clippings, religious affiliations, 95th Congress, 1976 December (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 20)
    - Clippings, religious discrimination in education, 1971 May (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 21)
    - Clippings, school aid obstruction, 1961 June (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 22)
    - Clippings, the Supreme Court decision on prayer, 1964 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 23)
    - Clippings, tuition tax credit, 1977-1978 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 24)
    - Congressional Budget Office, 1977 January-1977 October (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 25)
    - Congressional record, School Assistance Act of 1961, May 1961; Kennedy Education Bill, August 1961; A New Approach to Educational Aid/Aid to Education, August 1961-January 1962 (sealed envelope); Congressional Record, Federal Aid to Education 1962; Federal Aid to Education, March 1962; Aid to Education, June 1962; Extension, August 1962-January 1963; Federal Aid to Education 1963; Health Professionals Educational Assistance Act 1963, A pril 1963; Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963, August 1963; Higher Education Act of 1965, August 1965; Attacks to undermine voucher plan, February 1971; Tuition Tax Relief Act, May-September 1977, 1961-1977 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 26)
    - Congressional Research Service, legislative status checklist, 1971 April-1971 June (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 27)
    - The Conservative Party of New York, on Federal Aid, 1966 October (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 28)
    - Constitutional amendments, July 1963, 1963 July (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 29)
    - Cusack, Lawrence, 1963 May (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 30)
    - Danahy, Joseph, December 1961-September 1967, 1961 December-1967 September (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 31-32)
    - Debate, Bailey, John and Miller, William E., 1961 August (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 33)
    - Delaney and aid to education, research paper by student, 1961-1963 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 34)
    - Delaney’s Junior G.I. Bill/H.R. 320, 1962 February-1964 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 35)
    - Delaney’s Junior G.I. Bill/H.R. 320 requests, 1963 February-1964 July (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 36)
    - Delany, Frank J., 1961 June-1963 October (Box 7 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 37)
    - Delaney legislation, bills introduced, 91st-94th Congress, 1970 October (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 1)
    - Delaney legislation, 95th Congress, 1972 May-1976 November (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 2)
    - Duggan, Mae, 1967 December (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 3)
    - Dure, Leon, January-March 1962, 1962 January-1962 March (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 4)
    - Dwight, M.E., July-August 1967, 1967 July-1967 August (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 5)
    - Education Research and Statistics, 1965-1970 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 6-10)
    - Education Research and Statistics, 1970-1972 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 11)
    - Education Research and Statistics, 1973-1976 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 12)
    - Education vouchers, 1970 February-1971 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 13-14)
    - Elementary and Secondary Education Act of 1965, 1977 April (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 15)
    - Elementary and Secondary Education Act Title I Programs (Report), 1974-1976 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 16)
    - Federal aid to education, 1961 December-1963 October (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 18)
    - Federal aid to non public schools, Constitutional background, 1960-1965 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 19)
    - Federal aid to non public schools, Constitutional background, 1966-1971 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 20)
    - Federal aid and catholic schools publications, 1960-1965 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 21)
    - Federal aid to parochial schools, 1961-1970 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 22-24)
    - Federal aid to parochial schools, New York, 1970 February-1972 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 25)
    - Federal documents on church and state issues, 1960-1970 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 26)
    - Federal education programs, Washington Memo1, 1970 February-1971 December (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 27)
    - Federal legislation and education in New York state, November 1976-1977, 1976 November-1977 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 28)
    - Fuller, Edgar, 1964 March (Box 8 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 29)
    - Galvin, Thomas F., 1962 March-1963 January (Box 9 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 1)
    - Gilligan, William, 1962 January-1962 February (Box 9 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 2)
    - Health Professions Educational Assistance Act, 1962 August-1963 May (Box 9 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 3)
    - Higher Education, correspondence, 1972 June (Box 9 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 4-5)
    - Higher Education Facilities Act of 1962, 1963 August-1964 April (Box 9 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 6)
    - Higher Education Student Assistance Act, S. 1567, 1568, 2490, 3140, 1963 February-1964 August (Box 9 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 7)
    - Higher Education and National Affairs, 1971-1972 (Box 9 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 8)
    - H. Res. 591, Aviation: Resolution Commemorating Lindberg Flight, 95th Congress, May 1977. Includes correspondence and press release; H.R. 8103, Transportation Projects for National Parks, 95th Congress, June 1977; H. Con. Res. 318, Summer Olympic Games 1984, 95th Congress, July 1977. Includes correspondence and a Congressional Record; H.R. 8628, Summer Olympic Games Authorization Act of 1977, 95th Congress, July 1977; H. Res. 8754, Unemployment Compensation Cost Equalization Act, 95th Congress, August 1977; H.R. 9561, Veterans’ Educational Equity Act, 95th Congress, October 1977; H. Con Res. 811, L ou Gehrig Disease Resolution, 95th Congress, October 1977; H.R. 10512, Allow FDA to Ban Hair dyes, 95th Congress, January 1978; H. Res. 1012, Providing Funds for the Committee on Rules, 95th Congress, February 1978, Pacific/Asian American Heritage Week Resolution, September 1977, Resolution against Taxation of Fringe Benefits, September 1977, U.S. Relations with Communist Vietnam, September 1977 (Box 9 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 9)
    - Legislative outline 91st-94th Congress, 1975 January (Box 9 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 10)
    - Little, Msgr. Thomas, 1966 November (Box 9 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 11)
    - Maryland case, federal aid to education, 1963 September-1966 November (Box 9 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 12)
    - McCaffrey, J.B., 1962-1969 (Box 9 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 13)
    - Meet the Press, Ribicoff, Abraham, NBC television and radio broadcast. Transcript., 1962 June (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 1)
    - National Council of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1971 July (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 2)
    - National Education Association, 1965-January 1972 (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 3)
    - Non-Government Aid to Education, 1965 June (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 4)
    - President Nixon’s education message, 1970 March (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 5)
    - Publication, New York State Education Department, 1971-1976 (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 6)
    - Office of Non Public Education, 1977 July (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 7)
    - Old St. Peter’s Church, monograph Series, 1785-1935 (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 8)
    - Parochiaid, 1969 November-1972 February (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 9)
    - Powell, Adam C., 1963 June-1963 August (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 10)
    - Religion and the Constitution, 1962 June-1962 October (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 11)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham, 1962 March-1962 October (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 12)
    - The role of catholic schools, 1967 (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 13)
    - Spellman, Cardinal, 1962 January-1964 September (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 14)
    - Tuition tax credit, 1978 February-1978 March (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 15)
    - Tuition vouchers/Junior G.I. Bill, 1975-1977 (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 16)
    - The voucher system, 1971 (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 17)
    - Woodman, Robert P., 1967 January-1967 February (Box 10 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 18)
  - Subject Files; Arranged Chronologically, 1950-1978; 1.3
    - H.R. 7904, National Defense Education Act Amendment of 1961, 87th Congress, 1961 May-1961 July (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 1)
    - H.R. 8471, Educational Assistance Act of 1961, 87th Congress, 1961 May-1961 August (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 2)
    - 3, 1961 August (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder H.R. 8900, College Academic Facilities Act, 87th Congress)
    - H.R. 8890, Emergency Educational Aid Act, 87th Congress, 1961 August-1961 September (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 4)
    - H.R. 9896, School Children’s Assistance Act of 1962, 87th Congress, 1962 January (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 5)
    - H.R. 10180, 10390, 87th Congress, February 1962. H.R. 10180, Educational Finance Act of 1962 (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 6)
    - H.R. 3000, National Education Improvement Act of 1963, 88th Congress, 1963 January (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 7)
    - H.R. 4955, Vocational Education Act of 1963, 88th Congress, 1963 March-1964 January (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 8)
    - H.R. 6074, “Shared Time”/ National Defense Education Act of 1958, 88th, 1963 May-1963 June (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 9)
    - Rule Committee Resolutions: 86th-88th Congress, 1st Session, 1964 (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 10)
    - H. Res. 33, Joint Committee to Investigate Crime, 91st, 1969 January (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 11)
    - H.R. 165, Irish Immigration, 91st, 1969 January (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 12)
    - H.J. Res. 381, Susquehanna River Basin Compact, 91st Congress, 1969 February (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 13)
    - H.J. Res. 482, Mid Atlantic States Air Pollution Control Compact, 1969 February (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 14)
    - H.R. 6489, Head of Household Tax Bill, 91st, 1969 February (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 15)
    - H.R. 14944, 6201, 2572, H. Con. 572 H.R. 14944, To Separate Social Security from Welfare Reform and Add 20% Cash Increase, May 1972, H.R. 6201, To Prohibit Obscene Mail, 91st, February 1969, H.R. 2572, U.N. Expenses for NYC, January 1971, H. Con. Res. 572, Israeli Aircraft, 91st, April 1970, 1969 February-1972 May (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 16)
    - H.R. 3550, H. Res. 226, 616, H.R. 12513 H.R. 3550, To Disregard 20% Social Security Increase for Purpose of Passing Along Public Assistance Benefits, 93rd, February 1973, H. Res. 226, Condemning Execution of Jews in Iraq, 91st, February 1969, H. Res. 616, Peace Negotiations in the Middle East, 93rd, October 1973, H.R. 12513, To Provide Social Security Benefits Exclusive of Welfare Provisions, 92nd, January 1972, 1960 February-1973 October (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 17)
    - H.R. 6745, 9940, 337, 4244, 14853, 13648 H.R. 6745, To Increase Exemption to $1200, 90, February 1969, H.R. 9940, Tax Relief for Singles, 94th, October 1975, H.R. 337, Tax Relief for Singles, H.R. 4244, Tax Relief for Singles, 93rd, February 1973, H.R. 14853, Tax Relief for Singles and Married Working Couples, 92nd, May 1972, H.R. 13648, Single Persons Tax Relief, 92nd, March 1972, 1969 February-1975 October (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 18)
    - H.R. 9124, 9172, 8769, 9505, 91st, March 1969 H.R. 9124, Increased Burial Expenses for Vets, H.R. 9172, National Cemetery System, H. R. 8769, Newspaper Preservation Act, H.R. 9505, To Control Commuter Immigrants, 91st, 1969 March 26 (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 19)
    - H. Res. 350, Select Committee on Bureau of Budget, 91st, 1969 March (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 20)
    - H.R. 3769, 4923, 8276, 1265, 3912 H.R. 3769, Federal Employees Insurance Benefits, 94th, February 1975, H.R. 4923, Social Security Coverage for Federal Employees, 93rd, February 1973, H.R. 8276, Higher Education Tax Bill, 91st, March 1969, H.R. 1265, Prohibit Most Favored Nation Treatment to Nations Who Deny Citizens (Soviet Jews) Right to Emigrate, 94th, January 1975, H.R. 3912, Oppression of Soviet Jews, 93rd, February 1973, 1969 March-1975 February (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 21)
    - H.R. 10297, Encourage Shipbuilding, 91st, 1969 April (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 22)
    - H.R. 10859, Tax Exemption: Servicemen in Korea, 91st, 1969 May (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 23)
    - H.R. 6980, 11188, 5738, 12688, H. Con. Res. 677. Includes H.R. 6980, To Liberalize Eligibility Requirements of Blind Persons to Receive Disability Insurance Benefits, 93rd, April 1973, H.R. 11188, Liberalize Social Security for the Blind, 91st, May 1969, H.R. 5738, Payment of Chiropractors under Social Security, 92nd, March 1971, H.R. 12688, Prohibit Cigarette Smuggling, 92nd, January 1972, H. Con. 677, Collection of Foreign Debt, 92nd, August 1972, 1969 May-1973 April (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 24)
    - H. Con. Res. 320/89, Ethnic Slander, 91st-92nd, 1969 August-1971 January (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 25)
    - H. Con. Res. 356, Prisoners of War, 91st, 1969 September-1973 April (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 26)
    - H. Con. Res. 513, H.R. 13667, 16998, H. Con. Res. 513, Anti Smut Day, 92nd, January 1972, H. R. 13667, Limitations of Court Jurisdiction in Cases of Obscenity, 91st, September 1969, H.R. 16998, Freedom of Immigration in the Soviet Union, 1969 September-October 1972 (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 27)
    - H.R. 14554, the Disposal of Nickel from the National Stockpile, 91st, 1969 October (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 28)
    - H.R. 15092, 15424/15640, 91st, H.R. 15092, To Revise Immigration, H.R. 15424/15640, To Amend Merchant Marine Act, 1969 December 4 (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 29)
    - H. Con. Res. 483, Israel, 91st, 1970 January (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, H. Res. 843, Committee on Education, 1970 February (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 31)
    - H.R. 16127, Increase in Rail Road Retirement Annuities, 91st, 1970 February (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 32)
    - H.R. 15828, To Prohibit the Disposal of Waste in New York Bight, 91st, 1970 February (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 33)
    - H.J. Res. 1118, To Establish a Joint Committee on Environmental Technology, 91st, 1970 March 09 (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 34)
    - H.R. 16796, To Establish Marine Sanctuaries, 1970 April (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 35)
    - H.R. 17221, H.R. 16946, To Amend the Clean Air Act, 91st, 1970 April (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 36)
    - H.R. 17277, S. 3135, Aid to American Indians, 1970 April-1970 June (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 37)
    - H.R. 17697, Hurricane Protection, 91st, 1970 May (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 38)
    - H.R. 17827, Orderly Trade in Textiles and Leather Footwear, 91st, 1970 May (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 39)
    - Correspondence, Fish and Wildlife Coordination Act, 93rd Congress, 1970 July (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 40)
    - H.J. Res. 1305, H.R. 11638, H. J. Res. 1045, July 1970-June 1974 H.J. Res. 1035, Waterfront/Airport Commission Compact, 91st, July 1970, H.R. 11638, Policeman’s Bill of Rights, 93rd, November 1973, H.J. Res. 1045, Eleanor Roosevelt’s Birthday, 93rd, 1970 July-1974 June (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 41)
    - H.R. 18972, Public Employees Relations Act, 91st, 1970 August (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 42)
    - H.J. Res. 4, Joint Committee on the Environment, 92nd, 1971 January (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 43)
    - H.J. Res. 225, National Week of Concern for P.O.W.S, 92nd, 1971 January (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 44)
    - H.R. 128, Delaney’s School Children’s Assistance Act of 1971, 92nd, 1971 January (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 45)
    - H.R. 1750, Lead Based Paint Poisoning Prevention Program, 92nd, 1971 January (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 46)
    - H.R. 165, Irish Immigration, 92nd, 1971 January (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 47)
    - H. Con. Res. 123, Vietnam Prisoners, 92nd, 1971 February (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 48)
    - H. Con. Res. 153, Public Health Service Hospitals, 92nd, 1971 February (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 49)
    - H.R. 3490, To Establish a National Cancer Agency, 92nd, 1971 February (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 50)
    - H.R. 4709, Indian Tribes Benefits, 92nd, 1971 February (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 51)
    - H.R. 4826, Exemption of Pension and Annuity Income, 92nd, 1971 February (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 52)
    - H. Res. 327, Select Committee to Investigate Energy Resources, 92nd, 1971 March (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 53)
    - H. Con Res. 418, H.R. 16569, H.R. 322, H.R. 14375, March 1971-June 1976 H. Con Res. 418, Calling for the American People to Boycott All French Products (Drug Traffic), 92nd, October 1971, H.R. 16569, To Tax and Otherwise Control Explosives, 91st, March 1970, H.R. 322, Require Disclosure of Ingredients on Food Labels, 94th, January 1975, H.R. 14375, Arab Boycott Bill, 1971 March-1976 June (Box 11 (1-Legislative Files, 1950-1978), Folder 54)